Slide 46.
Slide 47.
Slide 49.
Slide 41.
Slide 42.
Slide 43.
Slide 45.
Slide dungeons outsides users.
Slide 46.
Slide 49.
Slide 50.
Slide 51.
track to deliver our full-year guidance. We're progressing our indications for Repsido,
Unalamab, both potential multi-blockbuster assets, and we're focused on our second-half
pivotal readouts that remain on track that would allow us to raise our mid- to long-term
growth outlook. And with that, we'll open it up to questions.
Thank you. To ask a question, you will need to press star 1 and 1 on your telephone and wait
for your name to be announced. Please limit yourself to one question and return to the queue
for any follow-up. To withdraw your question, please press star 1 and 1 again. We will now
take the first question. And your first question today comes from the line of Peter Fedult from
BNP Paribas. Please go ahead. Thanks, Peter Fedult, BNP Paribas. I realise there's not much
incremental you can say re-upfunding phase 3 readouts, and I heard your comments on Delbrecht
Spires. So with that in mind, can we focus?
Based on the accelerated approval potential for VotaPlan in Huntington's, I know phase 3
planning underway, but do you have any visibility or ballpark timelines you can give us for when
FDA might make a decision on whether you can file early on the phase 2 data generated thus far?
Thank you. Yeah, thanks, Peter. So we're planning in the process of engaging with the FDA
on that phase 2 data. I think at this point, our base case remains that we would need to do the
phase 3 study. We're going to do the phase 3 study on the phase 2 data. We're going to do the
phase 4 study on the phase 2 data. So we're going to do the phase 3 study on the phase 2 data.
So we're going to do the phase 2 study on the phase 2 data. So no change on that expectation.
I don't have a specific timeline. I would expect it to happen in the second half to provide more
clarity. And I would also note that we continuously follow these phase 2 patients for
a longer duration as well, which could provide us additional data. You know, we do know the FDA's
recent decisions or recent guidances from some of other therapies that are available for—that
could be available for Huntington's disease, which certainly, I think, is something that we
I think, shows the FDA's openness if the data ultimately is compelling. So we certainly want
to have that engagement, but I wouldn't change our base case at this point that a phase three
study would be required. Thank you. Thank you. Our next question comes from the line of